ARTYOM ZAGOSKIN

iOS Developer

in https://linkedin.com/in/artyomzagoskin



https://github.com/Inxel



artyzago@gmail.com

Open-minded, flexible, mindfulness, collaborative iOS developer with 3+ years of experience. Participate in all phases of development: system design, UI and UX discussion, decomposition and development. Spending spare time exploring new technologies to use it in pet and work projects. Fascinated about my job.

LANGUAGES

English

Professional Working Proficiency

Russian

Native

CERTIFICATES

iOS Development

Napoleon IT Course 2019

FCE (CEFR Level - B2)

Cambridge University Press 2019

SKILLS

- Swift
- SwiftUI
- Multi-threading
- **Object-Oriented Programming**
- Protocol-Oriented Programming
- Collaboration
- Communication
- Time management
- Agile and Scrum workflow
- JIRA / Confluence / Git

EDUCATION

Computer and Information Sciences

2017 - 2021

South Ural State University

WORK EXPERIENCE

iOS Developer

2021 - present

Aviasales

- Worked with results page (results showing 1.5x faster) and ticket screen
- Develop hotel page (75% more bookings)
- Make UI with SwiftUI (previously UIKit without storyboards)
- Objective-C to Swift refactoring
- Work in team of 4 iOS developers
- MVVM architecture
- Code review
- Unit and snapshot tests

iOS Developer

2019 - 2021

Napoleon IT

- 1. Retail app:
 - Clean Swift (VIP) architecture
 - Worked in team of 2 iOS developers
 - Developed catalog, authorization, shop cart, etc.
- 2. Platform for local services and specialized jobs:
 - VIPER architecture
 - Worked with GoogleMaps and other frameworks
- Developed profile, task creating constructor, transactions history, etc.
- Localization
- Only one iOS developer
- 3. Initialization of app (MWVM + Coordinators).
- 4. Mentor.
- 5. Napoleon IT iOS course lecturer.